Captain we have a job for you and
your crew
Trade moves things from world to world It
helps
us build homes send food and travel
No one lives on this island It may
have oil or rocks with gold and silver
Find what's there Our company
can get these things sell them and make
money
You can build your own base and lead your
own crew Profit is the money
left after costs
you'll get 10 of that profit
Sound good
Hmm Oh you
want more Alright 15 Sound good
Again Oh alright
20 That's my last offer
We have a deal
Let me show you your crew First meet
Rho your first mate
Hi Captain I'm glad we're a team
This is a learning game We'll use
science math English and social studies
Ask questions Try things
Learn from what goes wrong
We don't know what's on the island That's
why we need you
to lead us
Ready Captain Let's fly
Captain look ahead